Register of the Gerald Lee Warren papers, 1956-1994
Hoover Institution Archives
Gerald Lee Warren papers
1956-1994
80062
Hoover Institution Archives
228 manuscript boxes, 1 oversize box, 31 envelopes, 11 sound cassettes, 4 sound discs (93.5 linear feet)
Correspondence, memoranda, reports, notes, press releases, press conference transcripts, press summaries, photographs, clippings, and other printed matter relating to American foreign and domestic policy during the presidential administrations of Richard M. Nixon and Gerald R. Ford, the Watergate affair, and the American press. Digital copies of select records also available at https://digitalcollections.hoover.org.
Warren, Gerald Lee, 1930-2015.
Access
Collection is open for research. Digital copies of select records also available at https://digitalcollections.hoover.org.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items, computer media, and digital files. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos, films, or digital files during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Materials were acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 1980, with an increment received in 1995.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the online catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Alternate Forms Available
Digital copies of select records also available at https://digitalcollections.hoover.org.
Related Collection(s)
Gerald Warren papers, Special Collections and Archives, University of California San Diego
Gerald L. Warren papers, Richard Nixon Presidential Library and Museum
Biographical Note
1930 August 17 Born, Hastings, Nebraska
1951 Editor, The Daily Nebraskan Member, Sigma Nu Fraternity
1951-1952 Reporter, Lincoln Star, Lincoln, Nebraska
1952 B.A. in journalism, University of Nebraska
1952-1956 Single engine pilot, squadron personnel officer and legal (non-professional) officer, United States Navy
1956 Reporter, Mill Valley Record, Mill Valley, California
1956-1961 Reporter and later assistant city editor, San Diego Union
1961-1963 Business representative, Copley News Service
1963-1968 City editor, San Diego Union
1968-1969 Assistant managing editor, San Diego Union
1969-1974 Deputy press secretary to President Richard Nixon
1971 Distinguished Service Award, Alumni Association, University of Nebraska
1974-1975 Deputy press secretary to President Gerald Ford
1975-1995 Editor, San Diego Union, San Diego, California
2004 Master's degree in theology, Virginia Theological Seminary
2015 March 20 Died, Arlington, Virginia
Scope and Content of Collection
Correspondence, memoranda, reports, notes, press releases, press conference transcripts, press summaries, photographs, clippings, and other printed matter relating to American foreign and domestic policy during the presidential administrations of Richard M. Nixon and Gerald R. Ford, the Watergate affair, and the American press.
Ford, Gerald R., 1913-2006.; Nixon, Richard M. (Richard Milhous), 1913-1994.; Audiotapes.; Journalism--United States.; Phonorecords.; United States--Foreign relations--1969-1974.; United States--Foreign relations--1974-1977.; United States--Foreign relations.; United States--Politics and government--1969-1974.; United States--Politics and government--1974-1977.; United States--Politics and government.; Watergate Affair, 1972-1974.
- Biographical File, 1956-1975 (Box 1)
  Scope and Contents note
  Clippings, correspondence, curriculum vitae, and memoranda relating to the life of Gerald Warren and his alma mater, University of Nebraska, arranged in alphabetical order by physical form.
  - Clippings (Box-folder 1: 1)
  - Correspondence
    - Undated (Box-folder 1: 2)
    - 1967 November (Box-folder 1: 3)
    - 1969
      - January-May (Box-folder 1: 4-8)
      - August (Box-folder 1: 9)
      - November (Box-folder 1: 10)
    - 1970
      - March (Box-folder 1: 11)
      - June (Box-folder 1: 12)
    - 1971 June-July (Box-folder 1: 13-14)
    - 1972 June (Box-folder 1: 15)
    - 1973 April-May (Box-folder 1: 16-17)
    - 1975
      - March-April (Box-folder 1: 18-19)
      - July (Box-folder 1: 20)
      - October (Box-folder 1: 21)
  - Curriculum vitae and profile (Box-folder 1: 22)
  - Memoranda, undated (Box-folder 1: 23)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Announcements (Box-folder 1: 24)
    - Brochures (Box-folder 1: 25)
    - Cards and messages (Box-folder 1: 26)
    - General (Box-folder 1: 27)
    - Membership passes (Box-folder 1: 28)
    - Passport and voter registration applications (Box-folder 1: 29)
    - Poems (Box-folder 1: 30)
    - Posters (Box-folder 1: 31)
    - Press releases (Box-folder 1: 32)
  - University of Nebraska
    - Brochures
      - 1969 February (Box-folder 1: 33)
      - 1971-1972 (Box-folder 1: 34)
    - Clippings, 1971 March (Box-folder 1: 35)
    - Commencement, 1971 June (Box-folder 1: 36)
    - Correspondence
      - Undated (Box-folder 1: 37)
      - 1970 February (Box-folder 1: 38)
      - 1971 March-May (Box-folder 1: 39-42)
      - 1972 December (Box-folder 1: 43)
    - General (Box-folder 1: 44)
    - Invitations
      - 1970 April (Box-folder 1: 45)
      - 1971 June (Box-folder 1: 46)
    - Memoranda
      - 1971
        - March-April (Box-folder 1: 47-78)
        - June (Box-folder 1: 49)
      - 1972 December (Box-folder 1: 50)
    - Newsletters
      - 1968 June (Box-folder 1: 51)
      - 1971 March-April (Box-folder 1: 52-53)
    - News summaries, undated (Box-folder 1: 54)
    - Remarks, 1971 February-March (Box-folder 1: 55-56)
    - Schedules
      - Undated (Box-folder 1: 57)
      - 1971
        - February-March (Box-folder 1: 58-59)
        - June-July (Box-folder 1: 60-61)
    - Statements, 1971 February (Box-folder 1: 62)
    - Telegrams, 1969 January (Box-folder 1: 63)
- Speeches and Writings, 1969-1976 (Box 2)
  Brochures, clippings, correspondence, holograph notes, memoranda, newsletters, outlines of speeches, press releases, printed matter, schedules, and telegrams, arranged in chronological order.
  - "Importance of defense and the role of the public affairs officer,", undated (Box-folder 2: 1)
    Talking points for Gerald Warren. Typescript.
  - Speech, San Diego chapter of the Sigma Delta Chi, Little Bavaria restaurant near Del Mar, San Diego, California, 1969 September 5 (Box-folder 2: 2)
    Clipping.
  - Speech, Kogo-Junior League public service seminar, House of Hospitality, Balboa Park, San Diego, California, 1969 September 24 (Box-folder 2: 3)
    Press release. Typescript and printed copy.
  - Speech, North Dakota Press Association, Grand Forks, North Dakota, 1975 February 10 (Box-folder 2: 4)
    Printed copy. Includes correspondence with Al Austin.
  - Speech, Colorado Press Association's annual convention, Brown Palace Hotel, Colorado, 1975 February 23 (Box-folder 2: 5)
  - Speaker, Sam Rayburn Public Affairs symposium, East Texas State University, Commerce, Texas, 1975 April 1-2 (Box-folder 2: 6)
    Brochures, correspondence, clippings, memoranda, and printed copy.
  - Speech, Texas Intercollegiate Press Association annual convention, Hilton Inn, Amarillo, Texas, 1975 April 10-12 (Box-folder 2: 7)
    Correspondence, memoranda, schedule, clipping, and notes.
  - Address, joint dinner meeting of the Society of Professional Journalists, Sigma Delta Chi, the Public Relations Society of America and the Public Relations Club of San Diego, Cuyamaca Club, San Diego, 1975 April 13 (Box-folder 2: 8)
  - Speech, Washington Workshops Congressional seminars, sixth session seminar, Executive Office Building, Washington, D.C., 1975 April 18 (Box-folder 2: 9)
    Note and list of participants.
  - Guest speaker, Norfolk Jaycees Media Awards banquet, Admiralty Motor Hotel, Norfolk, Virginia, 1975 April 30 (Box-folder 2: 10)
    Correspondence, memoranda, and printed copy.
  - Speech, U.S. Suburban Press Publishers annual conference, Drake Hotel, Chicago, Illinois, 1975 June 25 (Box-folder 2: 11)
    Brochures, correspondence, clipping, printed copy, press release, and schedule.
  - Address, Oregon Press Newspaper Association, Bend, Oregon, 1975 July 11 (Box-folder 2: 12)
    Correspondence, clipping, note, and schedule.
  - "Quo Vadis?," remarks to the Nebraska Press Association, Omaha, Nebraska, 1976 April 24 (Box-folder 2: 13)
    Typescript.
- Personal Office File, 1962-1975 (Boxes 2-27)
  Appointment diaries, clippings, correspondence, daily files including holograph notes, interviews, invitations, meetings, memoranda, newsletters, press briefings, press conferences, press releases, printed matter, remarks, schedules, statements, telegrams, television reports, and travel itineraries of Gerald Warren, arranged in alphabetical order by physical form. Includes Gerald Warren's resignation from the White House press office under President Gerald Ford.
  - Affidavits, 1969 December (Box-folder 2: 14)
  - Appointment diaries
    - 1972-1973 (Box-folder 2: 15-16)
    - 1974 (Box-folder 3: 1)
  - Calendars, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 3: 2-5)
  - Clippings
    - 1970 March (Box-folder 3: 6)
    - 1971
      - January (Box-folder 3: 7)
      - March (Box-folder 3: 8)
    - 1972 May (Box-folder 3: 9)
    - 1973 July (Box-folder 3: 10)
    - 1974
      - February (Box-folder 3: 11)
      - May (Box-folder 3: 12)
      - October-November (Box-folder 3: 13-14)
    - 1975
      - March-April (Box-folder 3: 15-16)
      - June (Box-folder 3: 17)
  - Correspondence
    - General (Box-folder 3: 18)
    - Unidentified (Box-folder 3: 19)
    - 1969
      - January-May (Box-folder 3: 20-24)
      - July-December (Box-folder 3: 25-30)
    - 1970
      - January-May (Box-folder 3: 31-35)
      - June-December (Box-folder 4: 1-7)
    - 1971 February-December (Box-folder 4: 8-18)
    - 1972
      - January-August (Box-folder 4: 19-26)
      - September-December (Box-folder 5: 1-4)
    - 1973 (Box-folder 5: 5-16)
    - 1974 (Box-folder 5: 17-28)
    - 1975
      - January-August (Box-folder 6: 1-8)
      - December (Box-folder 6: 9)
  - Daily files
    - Undated (Box-folder 6: 10-12)
    - 1962 December (Box-folder 6: 13)
    - 1969 (Box-folder 7: 1-12)
    - 1970
      - January-June (Box-folder 7: 13-18)
      - July-December (Box-folder 8: 1-6)
    - 1971
      - General (Box-folder 8: 7)
      - January-October (Box-folder 8: 8-17)
      - November-December (Box-folder 9: 1-2)
    - 1972
      - General (Box-folder 9: 3)
      - January-December (Box-folder 9: 4-15)
    - 1973
      - January-May (Box-folder 9: 16-20)
      - July-August (Box-folder 9: 21-22)
      - September-December (Box-folder 10: 1-4)
    - 1974
      - January-June (Box-folder 10: 5-10)
      - July-December (Box-folder 11: 1-6)
    - 1975
      - January-April (Box-folder 11: 7-10)
      - May-June 19 (Box-folder 12: 1-6)
      - June 20-30 (Box-folder 13: 1-2)
      - July-August (Box-folder 13: 3-5)
      - October-December (Box-folder 13: 6-8)
  - Interviews, 1975
    - February-April (Box-folder 13: 9-11)
    - June (Box-folder 13: 12)
    - August (Box-folder 13: 13)
  - Invitations
    - Undated (Box-folder 13: 14)
    - 1969-1970 (Box-folder 13: 15-16)
    - 1971-1972 (Box-folder 14: 1-2)
    - 1973
      - January-April (Box-folder 14: 3)
      - May-December (Box-folder 14: 4)
    - 1974-1975 (Box-folder 14: 5-6)
  - Meetings
    - 1970 December (Box-folder 14: 7)
    - 1971 September (Box-folder 14: 8)
    - 1972
      - January (Box-folder 14: 9)
      - July (Box-folder 14: 10)
      - November (Box-folder 14: 11)
    - 1973
      - August (Box-folder 14: 12)
      - October (Box-folder 14: 13)
    - 1974 May (Box-folder 14: 14)
    - 1975 November (Box-folder 14: 15)
  - Memoranda
    - Undated (Box-folder 14: 16)
    - 1967 March (Box-folder 15: 1)
    - 1969
      - January-February (Box-folder 15: 2-3)
      - April-December (Box-folder 15: 4-12)
    - 1970
      - January-August (Box-folder 15: 13-20)
      - September-December (Box-folder 16: 1-4)
        Includes telephone memoranda.
    - 1971
      - January-October (Box-folder 16: 5-14)
      - November-December (Box-folder 17: 1-2)
    - 1972 (Box-folder 17: 3-14)
    - 1973
      - January-March (Box-folder 17: 15-17)
      - April-December (Box-folder 18: 1-9)
    - 1974
      - January-August (Box-folder 18: 10-17)
      - October-December (Box-folder 18: 18-20)
    - 1975
      - January-February (Box-folder 18: 21-22)
      - March-July (Box-folder 19: 1-5)
        Includes printed copy and typescript.
      - December (Box-folder 19: 6)
  - Miscellaneous, cards and messages (Box-folder 19: 7)
  - Newsletters, 1975 March (Box-folder 19: 8)
  - Press briefings
    - Undated (Box-folder 19: 9)
    - 1969 December (Box-folder 19: 10)
    - 1970
      - April-May (Box-folder 19: 11-12)
      - July (Box-folder 19: 13)
      - September-October (Box-folder 19: 14-15)
      - December (Box-folder 19: 16)
    - 1971
      - January (Box-folder 19: 17)
      - March-July (Box-folder 19: 18-22)
      - September (Box-folder 19: 23)
      - November-December (Box-folder 19: 24-25)
    - 1972
      - January (Box-folder 19: 26)
      - May-June (Box-folder 19: 27-28)
      - August-December (Box-folder 19: 29-33)
    - 1973
      - April (Box-folder 19: 34)
      - June-October (Box-folder 20: 1-5)
      - December (Box-folder 20: 6)
        Draft.
    - 1974 January-July (Box-folder 20: 7-13)
    - 1975
      - March (Box-folder 20: 14)
      - May-June (Box-folder 20: 15-16)
  - Press conferences
    - Undated (Box-folder 20: 17)
    - 1970
      - January (Box-folder 20: 18)
      - March-December (Box-folder 20: 19-28)
        Includes conference call.
    - 1971
      - January-February (Box-folder 20: 29-30)
      - March-December (Box-folder 21: 1-10)
    - 1972
      - January-March (Box-folder 21: 11-13)
      - April-September (Box-folder 22: 1-6)
      - November-December (Box-folder 22: 7-8)
    - 1973
      - January-May (Box-folder 22: 9-13)
      - June-September 14 (Box-folder 23: 1-5)
      - September 17-29 (Box-folder 24: 1)
      - October-December (Box-folder 24: 2-6)
    - 1974
      - January-April (Box-folder 25: 1-4)
      - May 1-15 (Box-folder 25: 6)
      - May 16-31 (Box-folder 26: 1)
      - June-August (Box-folder 26: 2-4)
  - Press releases
    - 1972 December (Box-folder 26: 5)
    - 1974 May (Box-folder 26: 6)
  - Printed matter
    - Undated (Box-folder 26: 7)
    - 1967 May-June (Box-folder 26: 8-9)
    - 1969 August (Box-folder 26: 10)
    - 1970
      - January-February (Box-folder 26: 11)
      - July-August (Box-folder 26: 12-13)
      - December (Box-folder 26: 14)
    - 1972
      - January (Box-folder 26: 15)
      - June (Box-folder 26: 16)
    - 1973
      - February-March (Box-folder 26: 17-18)
      - June-July (Box-folder 26: 19-20)
      - October (Box-folder 26: 21)
    - 1974
      - General (Box-folder 26: 22)
      - May (Box-folder 26: 23)
      - November (Box-folder 26: 24)
    - 1975
      - General (Box-folder 26: 25)
      - March-July (Box-folder 26: 26-30)
  - Remarks
    - Undated (Box-folder 27: 1)
    - General, 1970 (Box-folder 27: 2)
  - Resignation
    - Correspondence
      - 1972 November (Box-folder 27: 3)
      - 1975 June (Box-folder 27: 4)
    - Meetings, 1975 July (Box-folder 27: 5)
      Includes holograph notes.
    - Interviews, 1975 July (Box-folder 27: 6)
    - Newsletters, 1975 June (Box-folder 27: 7)
    - Press releases, undated (Box-folder 27: 8)
  - Schedules
    - Undated (Box-folder 27: 9)
    - 1970 July (Box-folder 27: 10)
    - 1974
      - March-April (Box-folder 27: 11-12)
      - August (Box-folder 27: 13)
  - Statements
    - Undated (Box-folder 27: 14)
    - 1973
      - August (Box-folder 27: 15)
        Includes drafts.
      - October (Box-folder 27: 16)
    - 1974
      - January-February (Box-folder 27: 17-18)
      - August (Box-folder 27: 19)
  - Telegrams
    - Undated (Box-folder 27: 20)
    - 1969
      - February (Box-folder 27: 21)
      - September (Box-folder 27: 22)
    - 1970
      - April (Box-folder 27: 23)
      - September (Box-folder 27: 24)
    - 1971 February (Box-folder 27: 25)
    - 1972 January (Box-folder 27: 26)
    - 1973
      - May (Box-folder 27: 27)
        Holograph notes attached.
      - December (Box-folder 27: 28)
    - 1974
      - March (Box-folder 27: 29)
      - May-July (Box-folder 27: 30-32)
    - 1975 May-June (Box-folder 27: 33-34)
  - Television news reports, 1973 May (Box-folder 27: 35)
  - Travel
    - Arizona, 1974 November 14-16 (Box-folder 27: 36)
    - 1975
      - North Dakota and Minnesota, February 6-7
        - Clippings (Box-folder 27: 37)
        - Correspondence (Box-folder 27: 38)
        - General (Box-folder 27: 39)
        - Memoranda (Box-folder 27: 40)
        - Notes (holograph) (Box-folder 27: 41)
        - Schedules (Box-folder 27: 42)
      - Denver, February 20-23
        - Clippings (Box-folder 27: 43)
        - Correspondence (Box-folder 27: 44)
        - Fact sheets (Box-folder 27: 45)
        - Memoranda (Box-folder 27: 46)
        - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 27: 47)
        - Notes (holograph) (Box-folder 27: 48)
        - Printed matter (Box-folder 27: 49)
        - Schedules (Box-folder 27: 50)
          Holograph notes included.
        - Telegrams (Box-folder 27: 51)
      - San Diego, April 12-13
        - Clippings (Box-folder 27: 52)
        - Correspondence (Box-folder 27: 53)
        - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 27: 54)
        - Schedules (Box-folder 27: 55)
      - Illinois, schedules, June 25-26 (Box-folder 27: 56)
      - Indianapolis, schedules, June 27 (Box-folder 27: 57)
      - Oregon, schedules, July 11 (Box-folder 27: 58)
      - San Diego, schedules, September 23-24 (Box-folder 27: 59)
  - Wire releases
    - Undated (Box-folder 27: 60)
    - 1974
      - July (Box-folder 27: 61)
      - November (Box-folder 27: 62)
- White House Office File, 1969-1977 (Boxes 27-89)
  Brochures, bulletins, correspondence, executive orders, interviews, meetings, memoranda, messages to Congress, newsletters, news summaries, pool reports, press briefings, press conferences, press releases, printed matter, proclamations, remarks, reports, schedules, statements, telegrams, television news reports, testimonies, and travel itineraries, both domestic and foreign, relating to President Nixon and President Ford, their press offices, cabinet and other government officials, and papers relating to President Nixon's personal financial situation, arranged alphabetically by physical form.
  - Brochures, undated (Box-folder 27: 63)
  - Bulletins
    - 1968 September (Box-folder 27: 64)
    - 1969 April (Box-folder 27: 65)
    - 1970 November (Box-folder 27: 66)
    - 1971 February (Box-folder 27: 67)
  - Correspondence
    - Undated (Box-folder 27: 68)
    - 1969
      - February (Box-folder 27: 69)
      - May-June (Box-folder 27: 70-71)
      - August (Box-folder 27: 72)
      - October-November (Box-folder 27: 73-74)
        Includes telegram.
    - 1970
      - January-February (Box-folder 27: 75-76)
      - April (Box-folder 27: 77)
      - July (Box-folder 27: 78)
      - November-December (Box-folder 27: 79-80)
    - 1971
      - January-March (Box-folder 28: 1-3)
      - August-October (Box-folder 28: 4-6)
      - December (Box-folder 28: 7)
    - 1972
      - February-April (Box-folder 28: 8-10)
      - July-September (Box-folder 28: 11-13)
      - December (Box-folder 28: 14)
    - 1973
      - January (Box-folder 28: 15)
      - July-August (Box-folder 28: 16-17)
      - October-November (Box-folder 28: 18-19)
    - 1974
      - March (Box-folder 28: 20)
      - May (Box-folder 28: 21)
      - December (Box-folder 28: 22)
    - 1975
      - January (Box-folder 28: 23)
      - April (Box-folder 28: 24)
        Holograph.
      - June-July (Box-folder 28: 25-26)
      - September (Box-folder 28: 27)
  - Executive orders
    - 1970
      - March-September (Box-folder 28: 28-34)
      - November-December (Box-folder 28: 35-36)
    - 1971
      - January-February (Box-folder 28: 37-38)
      - May-June (Box-folder 28: 39-40)
    - 1972
      - February-June (Box-folder 28: 41-45)
      - August-December (Box-folder 28: 46-50)
    - 1973
      - January (Box-folder 28: 51)
      - March-December (Box-folder 28: 52-61)
    - 1974
      - January-July (Box-folder 28: 62-68)
      - September-October (Box-folder 28: 69-70)
    - 1975
      - March (Box-folder 28: 71)
      - May-June (Box-folder 28: 72-73)
  - Fact sheets
    - Undated (Box-folder 28: 74)
    - 1970 April (Box-folder 28: 75)
    - 1971 September (Box-folder 28: 76)
    - 1972 January (Box-folder 28: 77)
    - 1973
      - January (Box-folder 28: 78)
      - March (Box-folder 28: 79)
      - May (Box-folder 28: 80)
      - October (Box-folder 28: 81)
    - 1974
      - March (Box-folder 28: 82)
      - June (Box-folder 28: 83)
    - 1975 March (Box-folder 28: 84)
  - General (Box-folder 28: 85)
  - Interviews
    - Undated (Box-folder 28: 86)
    - 1969 November (Box-folder 28: 87)
    - 1971
      - January (Box-folder 28: 88)
      - March (Box-folder 28: 89)
      - April (Box-folder 29: 1)
      - December (Box-folder 29: 2)
    - 1972
      - February (Box-folder 29: 3)
      - October (Box-folder 29: 4)
    - 1973
      - February (Box-folder 29: 5)
      - June (Box-folder 29: 6)
    - 1974 May (Box-folder 29: 7)
    - 1975
      - March-April (Box-folder 29: 8-9)
        Includes printed copies.
      - May (Box-folder 29: 10)
      - July-August (Box-folder 29: 11-12)
  - Meetings
    - Undated (Box-folder 29: 13)
    - 1969
      - April-May (Box-folder 29: 14-15)
      - November (Box-folder 29: 16)
    - 1970
      - May (Box-folder 29: 17)
      - August (Box-folder 29: 18)
      - October-December (Box-folder 29: 19-21)
    - 1971
      - February (Box-folder 29: 22)
      - April-May (Box-folder 29: 23-24)
      - September (Box-folder 29: 25)
      - November (Box-folder 29: 26)
    - 1972
      - March (Box-folder 29: 27)
      - May-October (Box-folder 29: 28-33)
      - December (Box-folder 29: 34)
    - 1973
      - January-May (Box-folder 29: 35-39)
      - September (Box-folder 29: 40)
      - November-December (Box-folder 29: 41-42)
    - 1974 January-September (Box-folder 29: 43-51)
    - 1975
      - April (Box-folder 29: 52)
      - June (Box-folder 29: 53)
  - Memoranda
    - Undated (Box-folder 30: 1)
    - 1948 March (Box-folder 30: 2)
      Printed copy.
    - 1969
      - January-April (Box-folder 30: 3-6)
      - May (Box-folder 30: 7)
      - June-December (Box-folder 30: 8-14)
    - 1970 (Box-folder 30: 15-26)
    - 1971 (Box-folder 30: 27-38)
    - 1972 (Box-folder 30: 39-50)
    - 1973
      - January-March (Box-folder 30: 51-53)
      - May-December (Box-folder 30: 54-61)
    - 1974 (Box-folder 30: 62-73)
    - 1975
      - January-February (Box-folder 31: 1-2)
      - March (Box-folder 31: 3)
        Includes printed material.
      - April-July (Box-folder 31: 4-7)
  - Messages
    - 1969 February (Box-folder 31: 8)
    - 1970 April (Box-folder 31: 9)
    - 1971 April (Box-folder 31: 10)
    - 1972 September (Box-folder 31: 11)
    - 1973 September (Box-folder 31: 12)
    - 1974 August (Box-folder 31: 13)
    - 1975
      - January (Box-folder 31: 14)
      - March (Box-folder 31: 15)
  - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 31: 16)
  - Newsletters
    - 1968 August (Box-folder 31: 17)
    - 1972 November (Box-folder 31: 18)
    - 1973 February (Box-folder 31: 19)
    - 1975